BANGAH M'BAYI YANN

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER



PROFILE

I'm a web developer with expertise in front-end and back-end development . I design and develop web applications using the latest technologists to deliver the product with quality code . I remain at your disposal for any interview .

SKILLS

- Web Developpement: Javascript, Node JS, PHP, C, Python, HTM, CSS, SCSS, TypeScript, JQuery, JAVA
- Databases : MYSQL, SQL SERVER, MongoDB, Firebase
- Versionning Tools: GIT, GITLAB, GITHUB
- Project Management Tools : Trello, Airtable, Notion

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Developer Intern

GlobalTech Pvt • Inde, Remote

May. 2023 - Today

Main missions:

• Built responsive, accessible and dynamic web pages to enable users to easily navigate site.

Web Developer Intern

LetsGrowMore • Inde, Remote

Apr. 2023 – May 2023

Main missions:

- Using my experience with front-end development to create a Map Grid layout that has a navigation bar showing the user's name.
- · Interact with user data through an API

FullStack Developer Intern

Bharat Intern • Inde, Remote

Mar. 2023-Apr 2023

- Web Application Development
- Creation of Content Management Tool
- Project Management Tool: The Project includes the creation of a social network with a Framework where users can communicate with others. Users have the ability to assign tasks to other users

EDUCATION

Software Engineering

feb. 2022 -apr. 2023

ALX AFRICA -HOLBERTON SCHOOL • Nairobi, Kenya

Bachelor in Computer Science (BCS)

nov. 2019 -apr. 2023

Université Internationale de Cote d'Ivoire • Abidjan, Côte d'Ivoire

BACCALAURÉAT D july. 2019

Collège Adventiste Abidjan • Abidjan, Côte d'Ivoire

LANGUAGES

French English

CERTIFICATIONS

- Certificate of Completion par ALX AFRICA(HOLBERTON SCHOOL)
- Introduction to Cybersecurity from Cisco Networking Academy
- Get Connected from Cisco Networking Academy

CENTER OF INTERETS

Cybersecurity, Tennis, Video Games, Travel, Volunteering

BANGAH M'BAYI YANN

FULLSTACK DEVELOPPEUR



OBJECTIF

Je suis un développeur web ayant une expertise dans le développement front-end et Back-end. Je conçois et développe des applications Web en utilisant les dernières technologues pour livrer le produit avec un code de qualité. Je reste à votre disposition pour un éventuel entretien.

COMPÉTENCES

- Développement Web: Javascript, Node JS, Express JS, PHP, C, Python, HTML, CSS, SCSS, TypeScript, JQuery, JAVA
- Base de données : MYSQL, SQL SERVER, MongoDB, Firebase
- Outils de versionning : GIT, GITLAB ,GITHUB
- Outils de gestion de projet : Trello, Airtable, Notion

EXPÉRIENCE DE TRAVAIL

Web Developer Intern

GlobalTech Pvt • Inde, Remote

May. 2023 - Aujourd'hui

Principales missions:

 Création de pages web réactives, accessibles et dynamiques pour permettre aux utilisateurs de naviguer facilement sur le site.

Web Developer Intern

Principales missions:

LetsGrowMore • Inde, Remote

Ecto Crownword Indo, rterm

- Utiliser mon expérience avec le développement front-end pour créer une disposition de Grid de carte ayant une barre de navigation montrant le nom de l'utilisateur.
- Interagir avec les données de l'utilisateur grâce a une API

FullStack Developer Intern

Bharat Intern • Inde, Remote

Mar. 2023- Avr 2023

Avr. 2023 – Mai 2023

- · Développement d'application web
- · Création d'Outil de gestion de contenu
- Outil de gestion de projet : Le projet inclus la création d'un réseau social avec un Framework ou les utilisateurs peuvent communiquer avec les autres. Les utilisateurs ont la possibilité d'assigner des taches a d'autres utilisateurs

FORMATION

Software Engineering

fev. 2022 - avr. 2023

ALX AFRICA -HOLBERTON SCHOOL • Nairobi, Kenya

Licence en Informatique et Sciences du Numérique (ISN)

nov. 2019 - avr. 2023

Université Internationale de Cote d'Ivoire • Abidjan, Côte d'Ivoire

BACCALAURÉAT D juil. 2019

Collège Adventiste Abidjan • Abidjan, Côte d'Ivoire

LANGUES

Français Anglais

CERTIFICATIONS

- Certificate of Completion par ALX AFRICA(HOLBERTON SCHOOL)
- Introduction a la Cybersecurite de Cisco Networking Academy
- Get Connected de Cisco Networking Academy

CENTRE D'INTERET

Cybersecurite, Tennis, Jeux vidéo, Voyages, Bénévolat